export const bpscQuestionsEnglish = [
    {
        question: "Who was the first Chief Minister of Bihar?",
        options: ["Dr. Sri Krishna Sinha", "Jagannath Mishra", "Laloo Prasad Yadav", "Nitish Kumar"],
        correctAnswer: "Dr. Sri Krishna Sinha",
        },
        {
        question: "Which river is known as the lifeline of Bihar?",
        options: ["Ganges", "Yamuna", "Kosi", "Sone"],
        correctAnswer: "Ganges",
        },
        {
        question: "The famous 'Bihar School of Yoga' is located in which district?",
        options: ["Madhubani", "Munger", "Patna", "Bhagalpur"],
        correctAnswer: "Munger",
        },
        {
        question: "The capital of Bihar is:",
        options: ["Patna", "Gaya", "Muzaffarpur", "Bhagalpur"],
        correctAnswer: "Patna",
        },
        {
        question: "In which year did Bihar become a separate state after the partition of Bihar and Jharkhand?",
        options: ["2000", "1999", "1995", "2002"],
        correctAnswer: "2000",
        }
    ];


export const bpscQuestionsHindi = [
        {
            question: "बिहार के पहले मुख्यमंत्री कौन थे?",
            options: ["डॉ. श्री कृष्णा सिन्हा", "जगन्नाथ मिश्रा", "लालू प्रसाद यादव", "नितीश कुमार"],
            correctAnswer: "डॉ. श्री कृष्णा सिन्हा",
            },
            {
            question: "किस नदी को बिहार की जीवनरेखा कहा जाता है?",
            options: ["गंगा", "यमुना", "कोसी", "सोन"],
            correctAnswer: "गंगा",
            },
            {
            question: "'बिहार स्कूल ऑफ योग' किस जिले में स्थित है?",
            options: ["मधुबनी", "मुंगेर", "पटना", "भागलपुर"],
            correctAnswer: "मुंगेर",
            },
            {
            question: "बिहार की राजधानी क्या है?",
            options: ["पटना", "गया", "मुजफ्फरपुर", "भागलपुर"],
            correctAnswer: "पटना",
            },
            {
            question: "किस वर्ष बिहार और झारखंड का विभाजन हुआ और बिहार एक अलग राज्य बना?",
            options: ["2000", "1999", "1995", "2002"],
            correctAnswer: "2000",
            }
        ];
        